Yahoo!
やっほー!
It's not yahoo.
やっほーじゃねーよ
Don't tell me you're here!
ここにいると言わない!
Every time.
毎回じゃん
I've never been on time.
時間通りに来たことない
No, I was on time the other day.
いや、この前は時間通りだった
Oh, really?
あ、ほんと?
You're wearing amazing colored pants again today.
今日またすげー色のパンツ履いてんじゃん、
Something.
なんか
I feel like it's a little noticeable.
ちょっと目立ったなって感じ
Yeah, that's right.
うん、そう
surely.
確かに
Eh, have you already decided what you want to buy?
え、なんかもう買いたいもん決まってんの?
I've noticed it a little bit.
ちょっと目もつけてきちゃった
Oh, really?
あ、ほんと?
So let's go inside.
だから中行こう
go?
行 く?
When I was told it was already green, I knew it instantly today.
もう緑って言われたらもう今日一発で分かったの
yes?
そう?
surely.
確かに
Isn't green cute?
緑かわいくない?
I quite like green.
緑結構好き
Well, certainly.
まあ確かに
Ah, one more.
あ、1個上じゃん
These two.
この2つ
cute.
かわいい
I don't have an image of it, so it's okay.
なんかイメージないから逆にいいんじゃん
It's okay because I don't usually have an image of it.
なんか普段もイメージないからいいんじゃん
Isn't it cute?
かわいくない?
cute.
かわいい
Are these three okay?
この3つでいい?
Highest.
最高
When they come, they take more and more money.
来るとどんどん金が取られる
I don't say that.
そういうこと言わない
dangerous.
あ ぶない
I wish I could buy something unexpected.
想定外のものまで買ってあげたらいい
Surprisingly.
意外に
Well, it does look good on you.
まあでも似合うんじゃん
real?
ほんと?
Okay, even if you're late, I'll make sure to buy something for you.
いいな、お前遅刻してきても なんかそれのちゃんと買ってもら
Yes.
えて
thank you.
ありがとう
That's good.
いい な
I'm about to be robbed of my money.
もう俺金むしられるばっかじゃん
I don't say that.
そういうこと言わない
Would you like me to return it to you with my body?
ちゃんと体で返してもらおうか
I agree.
そうだね
The one who climbed up ahead.
この先登っていった方
Well, it looked better than I expected.
てか想定外に似合ったな、それ
real?
ほんと?
It suited me beyond my expectations.
想定外に似合った
Take that off for a moment.
ちょっとそれ脱いでみて
a,
あ、
That's good.
いい じゃん
cute?
かわいい?
Yay, thank you.
わーい、ありがとう
When I first met you, I felt really tired.
初めて会った時すげーだるぎできたもんな
Let's stop that.
それはやめとこう
I won't say it.
言わない
I will do my best and grow from now on.
これから頑張って成長します
Oh, are you wearing those?
あ、それ履いてんのか
I don't need it.
いらねーな
Shall I go for a while?
とりあえずちょっと行くか
Okay.
オッケー
Has it changed?
かわった?
This outfit is cute.
かわいい、この服
I want to wear it every day.
毎日着たい
Which one is better?
どっちがいいの?
What color was this?
これ何色あったっけ?
It's kind of gray.
なんかグレーみたいなやつです
It was white.
白あった
Looks like it would go well with white.
白に合いそう
use.
使う
Just in case.
一応、念のため
I want to follow you around this much.
これくらいでついて歩きたいね
So, until now?
じゃあ、今までは?
What has happened so far?
今までは何?
He's a kid.
ガキだよ
I don't say that.
そういうこと言わない
Stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立って
This is Rina.
りなです
It's 22.
22です
adult?
大人?
Is 22 an adult?
22って大人?
A kid?
ガキか
It looks a little more mature.
ちょっと大人っぽくなります
Cooperate.
協力して
Oh, this?
あ、これ?
You don't need it.
いらんでしょ
Isn't it better to hurry up?
あんま早くいいのないか
what?
何?
That's it.
あれでしょ
Just barely.
ギリギリ
Take it thoroughly.
ガッツリとる
Isn't it invisible?
見えなくない?
Can't you see?
見えない?
I ate a little too much.
ちょっと食べ過ぎた
I ate too much.
食べ過ぎた
which one?
どれ?
Oh, this?
あ、これ?
Down below.
下に
It's so good.
すぐったい
This goes down.
これ下がる
Super supportive.
超サポリー
Look here.
こっち見て
yeah?
ん?
what?
何?
I'm not tutsage.
ツッツアゲしてないよ
I'm not kidding.
ツ ッツアゲしてないよ
Sealet was increasing in various ways.
シーレット色々増えていってたよ
I found out.
バレた
If you were at the supermarket, you'd be the type to pop it into a cabon.
スーパーにいたらカボンの中にポンポン入れるタイプでしょ
of course.
もちろん
Isn't it sea?
シーじゃないか
Don't you really understand?
あんまわかんないか
So it fits well?
だから収まりがいい?
Cho
ちょ
It's so good.
う どいい
Natural.
自然ね
Hey.
ねえ
It's really embarrassing to be photographed close up.
そこはアップで撮られるのめっちゃ恥ずかしい
yeah?
ん?
It's closed.
閉じんだよ
Why did you close it?
なんで閉じんだよ
soft?
柔らかい?
Okay then.
じゃあいいでしょ
If you haven't taken a picture, it's really beautiful.
撮ってない方めっちゃ綺麗だよね
real?
ほんと?
Awesome.
すげーし
Are you holding it?
握ってんの?
I'm not holding it.
握ってない
Oh, what happened?
あ、 どうしたの?
It doesn't hit there.
そこ当たらない
This way?
こっち?
Yeah.
うん
What is that?
な にそれ?
I just came out.
ちょうど出てんだけど
What is that?
なにそれ?
This is amazing.
すげーなこれ
This is so closed.
めちゃくちゃ閉まってるよこれ
It's a little different than usual.
いつもとちょっと違うんです
What is that?
なにそれ?
Haven't you seen it?
見たことない?
Big.
おっきい
But it's in.
でも入っちゃってる
What is that movement?
なにその動き
その動きなにこれ
What is that?
な にそれ
Because it's tightened inside, it doesn't move very well.
中で締めるから、 動きがあんまりよろしくないんだから
sorry.
ごめん
Was there a place that felt the best?
一番気持ちいいとこあったの?
Ah, this is terrible.
あ、これやばいよね
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
ぶりぶりされてる
What is dangerous?
やばいってなに?
That's dangerous, isn't it?
やばいでしょ
Of course it's dangerous.
もちろんやばい
Show me the whites of your eyes.
白目を見せて
what?
な に?
Do I have to say it?
言わなくていい?
picture?
え?
You don't have to say it.
言わなくていい
Sometimes it stays the same even when I take pictures.
たまに写真撮るときもそのままになるもん
I won't say that.
なんて言わない
Oh, this is terrible.
あ、これやばい
It's so hot.
いっちゃいちゃいちゃ
Let's stop this.
これ止めようや
what?
なに?
I'll stop now.
これで止めるの
how?
どうやって?
Not moving?
動きない?
Tighten it
締めてこ
stomach.
い
Look over here.
こ っち向いて
You look nice.
いい格好してんじゃん
I like the back.
奥がいいな
中間
I like the middle.
中間がいいな
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Good looking.
いい 格好してるよ
Ah, this is terrible.
あ、 これ 中間やばい
Enough?
もういい?
I shot it without permission.
勝手に撃っちゃった
Her pussy is really open.
めっちゃマンコ開いてる
You're kidding.
ふざけてんじゃん
You've thoroughly explored the inside of her pussy, haven't you?
マンコの中をしっかり探検してきたでしょ
It's true.
ほんとだ
And isn't it cute?
しかも可愛くないでしょ
Aren't you a foreigner?
外人さんじゃない?
Shall I bring it?
持ってく?
I don't need it.
いらない
It's not enough.
物足りないんじゃん
different.
違う
Ah, it moved on its own.
あ、勝手に動いた
Are you that close?
そんなに近づく?
Ah, that's completely different.
あ、全然違うところだ
hey.
ね
It's in the monthly edition.
月 版になってる
a,
あ、
terrible.
や ばい
やばい
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Ah, that went very well.
あ、 あ まり よくいっちゃった
Oh, go.
あ、いって
Ah, that's deep.
あ、それ奥ついてる
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
You suddenly got into it, didn't you?
急に奥ついたでしょ
It doesn't feel right, but it feels good,
なんか、ついてないんだけど、気持ちよくて、
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
Oh, no.
あ、駄目だよ
I'll move it.
動かしちゃう
what?
何?
I'll tell you when I move it.
動かしたら言っちゃうよ
why?
なんで?
I'll tell you if I move it.
動かしたら言っちゃう
copper
どう
Did you do it?
した の?
I don't have the energy today.
今日、体力ないし
why?
なんで?
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
I'll go to you.
俺に行くから
That's it too.
それもそれ
white.
白
It's almost white.
なんか白だくらいだね
Smack.
びしゃびしゃ
Hey.
ねぇ
We're having sex.
セックスしてるわ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Is it correct?
当たってる?
That's right.
当たってる
Oku, you're right.
奥、当たってる
Please follow me now.
もう、ついてください
Yeah, wait.
うん、待って
Please follow me.
ついてください
Hey.
ねぇ
Do you like sex?
セックス好き?
like.
好 き
Please follow me a lot.
いっぱいついてください
Please follow me as much as possible.
い っぱいついてください
My legs are terrible.
足やばい
why?
なんで?
I'm really shaking.
めっちゃ震えてる
Why are you shaking?
なんで震えてるの?
this.
これ
I'm concerned.
懸念してる
what happened?
どうしたの?
this.
これ
It's delicious.
うますぎー
what happened?
どうしたの?
this.
これ
Really.
めっちゃ
Hey.
ねぇ
Stop it.
やめて
What is this?
なにこれ
Why are you shaking like this?
なん でこんな震えてるの?
It makes me tremble.
震えちゃうんだよ
Are you shaking?
震えちゃうの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Because I stretched it out.
伸ばしたからね
Are you feeling tired?
つってはいない?
I'm not tired.
つってないよ
I'm just shaking.
ただ震えてるだけ
Do you accept?
うけんの?
Hmm.
うーん
sorry.
す み ません
すみません
Please take it out.
出してください
Do you say it properly?
ちゃんと言う?
So please take it out.
だから出してください
I was served.
出されちゃった
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Today was a day when I didn't have much energy.
今日は体力がない日でした
yeah?
ん?
It was a day when my physical strength was weak.
体力が弱々な日でした
I was really pushing myself.
めっちゃ押しきれてたもん
yes.
そう
terrible.
やばい
It's time, so for now.
時刻したから、とりあえず
Anyway, it was time.
とりあえず時刻したから
Is that where it starts?
そこスタートか
start.
スタート
It's because of that.
それ のせい
Sorry.
ごめんね
Feeling guilty, even to some extent, makes you weak.
多少なりとも、こうなんか罪悪感があると弱々になるんでしょ
I'm sorry.
すみませんでした
I don't give it out.
出 さない
I'll be careful.
気をつけます
please forgive me.
許してください
You're fine.
元気だね
yeah?
ん?
You're fine.
元気だね
It's a bicycle.
自転車だもん
Seriously?
まじ?
That's terrible.
やばいね
Which would be better?
どこがいいかな?
Also, let's consult and find out.
また、相談、見つけよう
This has nice lines
これ、線感がきれい
That's right.
だ ね
beautiful?
きれい?
beautiful.
きれい
From here in black.
黒いこっから
Yes.
はーい
it hurts.
痛 い
yeah?
ん?
It hurts here, so do an uppercut.
こっちに痛いから、アッパーして
Uppercut.
アッパーかい
yeah?
ん?
Uppercut.
アッパーかい
cold.
冷たい
Somehow, I ended up taking it home with me inside the mancon.
なんか、マンコンの中、持ち帰ることになる
Please stand up.
立ってね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yeah?
ん?
This is important.
ここ、大事だもん
Ah, I'll take it home with me.
あ、大事に持って帰る
It's important to wash it.
洗うのが大事だもん
Next, wash me too.
次に、俺も洗って
Ah.
あっ
What, if I was alone, it would be over.
何、一人だったら終わってる
Next time?
今度は?
yeah?
ん?
Next time?
今度は?
Just right.
ちょうどいい
I can go right away.
早速、行ける
I went.
行っちゃった
I went there.
行ったもん
It's sunny for a while.
ちょっと、晴れた
It might be hot.
暑いかも
When it's cold, taking a bath is the best thing.
寒い時、お風呂も一番
But it's cold when you get up there.
でも、上がったら寒いんだよね
Maybe a spray.
多分、スプレー
in?
で?
It's like a styling agent.
なんか、スタイリング剤みたいな
Oh, that kind of thing?
あ、そういうやつ?
Yeah.
うん
But I was told that it would be fine if I put it on.
でも、つけたらいいよ、って言われて
Yeah, you can put it on.
うん、つけたらいい
Is it fun when you go shopping for clothes even if you get teased?
かつなでされても、服買いに行くような時は楽しい?
Shopping is surprisingly fun.
意外とショッピング楽しい
hey.
ね
Well, just do it together normally.
てか、普通に一緒にやって
But I didn't feel like I had much of a choice.
でも、自分じゃあんまり選ばない感じだったから、
They say it's a bit new, but it suits them.
ちょっと、新鮮だけど似合うって言ってくれてるし
Yes, of course.
そう、もちろん
Really?
ほ んとに?
He doesn't look like a kid anymore.
ガキっぽさなくなってんじゃん
Or maybe you're just a kid.
それとも、ガキってことだよね
what?
何?
Do you usually want to say that you look like a kid?
普段、ガキっぽいって言いたい?
What?
何が?
He usually seems like a kid.
普段、ガキっぽいって
Having said that, I feel young.
そうは言って、若いなぁ、みたいな
Wait, are you getting older?
ちょっと、年齢上がった?
Yeah.
うん
Wait, are you getting older?
ちょっと、年齢上がった?
Is it okay to be more mature than age?
年齢、年齢っていうより大人っぽくなっていいの?
hey.
ね
surely.
確かに
It means it's on.
ついてるってことさ
Yeah.
うん
early.
早い
He always recovers this quickly.
いつもこんな復活早い
Yeah?
うん?
He always recovers this quickly.
いつもこんな復活早い
It's early.
早いって
Today is?
今日は?
It's early today.
今日は早い
It always changes so much.
いつもこんな、めっちゃ変わるよ
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it good?
いいじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
Also?
また?
Yeah.
うん
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
It has completely changed,
全然変わって、
I mean, wouldn't you like it if it was you?
なんか、 あんたでさ、入れたら好きじゃん?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, no, no, no.
あー、やばいやばいやばい
go.
いく
Okay.
いいよ
Well done.
よくできた
good.
よ かった
It's a house like this.
ちゃんとこういう家だ
Yeah.
うん
If I can only do it here, I won't come back here.
ここにしかできると、ここに帰らないし
Change your clothes a lot.
いっぱい服替える
Change clothes.
服替える
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ
What is it?
なんだよ
Have some Paimo before heading home.
帰る前にパイモで
At Paimo before going home at Paimo.
パイモで帰る前にパイモで
I took it.
取ったよ
取った
Is that so?
そう なの?
If I didn't like it more, it would be the one that felt the worst.
もっとが嫌いだったら、 最悪感感じたやつ
Ah, I think it's coming.
あ、届くみたい
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Like.
みたいな
when washing.
洗うときに
Wow, it's overflowing.
うわ、溢れる
How much should I replace?
どこまで置き換えたらいいの?
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
Will it take 4 more minutes?
あと4分かかるか?
It doesn't move.
動かない
Ah, good.
あ、いい
What is this shower?
このシャワー、何これ?
Ah, I touched it.
あ、触れた
With fingers and toes.
指足と指で
Did you learn how to use it?
使い方覚えた?
Put it here.
ここ入れて
Very vigorously.
めっちゃ勢いよく
Can you do it?
できるかな?
Born?
生まれた?
Should I remove it?
抜けばいいの?
Just leave it like this.
このままでいって
There's just a lot left.
結構残ってるだけ
Ah, but it's clean now.
あ、でもきれいになった
It's true.
本当だ
feeling.
感
It's about half now.
半分くらいになった
Didn't you smoke at the end?
最後、吸ったんじゃない?
Isn't that why you started smoking?
そういうことから吸ったんじゃない?
Because I smoked it.
吸ったから
Oh, but this.
え、でもこれ
When I got out, it was already dry.
出るともう乾かんでる
I didn't smoke again.
もう一回吸いなかった
This one is definitely better.
こっちの方が全然いいじゃん
I don't want to go out in this cold weather.
このままなく寒いとこ出たくない
Inhale again.
もう一回吸いなさい